<Document>
  # Gasses
  Gasses are a critical part of the station's operation, and the station's decay.
  You may know them as the stuff you breathe, but they are also relevant in many other ways

  Gasses have certain properties that make them useful for different tasks.

  ## Oxygen
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenTank" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="DoubleEmergencyOxygenTank" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ExtendedEmergencyOxygenTank" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="EmergencyOxygenTank" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

  A common gas, used by most species on the station to breathe.

  Oxygen is an oxidizer, which means it supports combustion.
  This makes it both useful when fusing gasses in a burn chamber, and dangerous when mixed with flammable gasses.

  ## Nitrogen
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenTank" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

  An inert gas, used in part with oxygen to create a breathable atmosphere.

  Nitrogen is very stable and comprises most of a standard breathable atmosphere.

  ## Air Mix
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirCanister" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirTank" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

  A mixture of gasses that is breathable to most species on the station.
  It consists of 21% oxygen and 79% nitrogen.

  ## Carbon Dioxide
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CarbonDioxideCanister" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

  A waste gas produced by the human respiration process. A common byproduct of combustion.

  ## Smoke
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ESTileFireStage4" Caption="A fire!!!"/>
  </Box>
  A gas created by combusting fires.

  Breathing it in over a certain threshold has a chance to cause [bold]smoke inhalation[/bold], which must be treated by breathing as much pure oxygen as possible.

  ## Water Vapor
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WaterVaporCanister" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  A common gas, produced by the burning of plasma and other processes.

  ## Plasma
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PlasmaCanister" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  A highly flammable gas that is used in many processes on the station.

  Engineering uses this gas to generate power and create exotic gasses.

  Burning it generates a lot of heat, as well as gas byproducts such as carbon dioxide and water vapor, depending on the efficiency of the burn.

  ## Ammonia
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmmoniaCanister" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  A gas produced by the decomposition of bodies.

</Document>
